

Prague, Czech Republic



lukas.bunat@gmail.com



+420 731 277 533



bunat.cz



bunatl



lukasbunat





Full-Stack & Software Developer

I am an enthusiastic developer with a passion for programming and technology. I have been in IT and specifically in software development for 4+ years. Right now, I am looking for an opportunity that will utilize and further expand my skillset. My focus is to build platforms that will help grow and scale any business needs.

I don't just code, thanks to my strong educational background, I have a wide range of skills like planning, theoretical informatics or analytical & theoretical thinking that helps me in finding clever solutions. I have had studied at many different universities all over the world and I take great pride in my international education. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges. I am always open to new opportunities and eager and open to learn more!



Technical Skills

Software development

Full-Stack technologies C, C++, JAVA SE, bash, AHK

Front End React.js 16.12, JavaScript ES6/2017, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS

Back End Node.js, express.js, JAVA EE, "REST APIs", apache2, nginx

Database SQL (MySQL, MS SQL Server), No-SQL (MongoDB - Mongoose, Monk)

Other Yarn, npm, webpack, parcel, babel, postman

Software Collaboration Theoretical informatics Computer architecture

Other

Tableau, Rapid Miner, Wolfram Alpha, Modelio, MS Office Suite, AutoCAD, Inventor

GIT, GitLab, JIRA, Trello, Slack, G Suite, MS Teams

Calculus, Linear Algebra, Algorithms, Speed and memory efficiency

Data and number representation, OS/memory/cache/FS management, multitasking

Business Intelligence, Testing, PC/WWW networking, UML Data analysis, Logical thinking, Critical & analytical thinking



Experiences

Work Experiences

Freelancer, "on and off" contracts 09/2019 - Present

Business websites

- **○** GitHub
- Web application (MERN)
- Personal full-Stack projects (JS, node.js, reactJS)
- Wordpress

Internal application Specialist 05/2018–05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s., Prague, Czech Republic

- O2TV platform and O2TV set-top box
- Company internal and external software and web application development
- https://www.o2tv.cz/, O2TV
- > Java EE, JS, HTML5, CSS3, C

Internships

Big Data Architect Trainee 10/2017–12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University, Madrid, Spain

- Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy
- PySpark, Jupyter, Hadoop

Network Engineer Trainee 03/2017-06/2017

- Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea
 - Network routing and latency simulations on COOJA Simulator
 - Wireshark, COOJA

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a tutor at international student club at Czech Technical University.



Soft Skills



New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic and passionate about learning new things and technologies



Decisiveness and good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Education

University, Year(s) of Study		Field of study, Faculty	Location
Story Exp	University of Economics	Information systems and technologies	Prague,
V PRAZE	2019 - Present	Faculty of informatics and statistics	Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague, Czech Republic
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	
(RES	University of Finance and Administration	Applied Informatics, Graduate, Bc.	Prague, Czech Republic
VOIO	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	
R 3 8	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague, Czech Republic
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	
THE PARTY OF THE P	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	Daegu, South Korea
	2017	College of IT Engineering	
ENT OF HECHOOR	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai, India
Ell. Wallets and St.	2016	Department of Computer Science	
TO THE PARTY OF TH	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	Delft, Netherlands
	2016	The ATHENS Programme	
	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth, United Kingdom
	2012		



Certificates







Autodesk AutoCAD (2014) Inventor (2014)



KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme